Maybe I was just too blind to see
All the spaces between you and me
Thinkin′ we were magical, we're meant to be
If only I heard what you gotta say
Wish that I could just turn back the time
Back when I was yours and you were mine
Hoping we′ll get better, we'll be fine somehow
By now
If only we don't choose to go
And stay a bit longer
Would things stay the same?
If only there′s another chance
I′ll make it all okay
Don't walk away
Now I′m just a guy with made-up fantasies
With all my dreams and possibilities
Trimmin' all the memories, ′cos you broke me when you leave
If only we don't choose to go
And stay a bit longer
Would things stay the same?
If only there′s another chance
I'll make it all okay
Don't walk away